Guide to the University of Pittsburgh Alumni Association Records, 1895-2012 UA.6.5.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Early History, 1895-1952; X.
  - Freshman Handbook, 1932-1933 (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - University of Pittsburgh Commencement Program, 1935 (Box 43, Folder 50)
  - "The Pitt Compass", 1950-1951 (Box 43, Folder 51)
  - "The Pitt Compass", 1951-1952 (Box 43, Folder 52)
  - Intramural Sports Handbook, 1951-1952 (Box 43, Folder 53)
- Other Records, 1983-2010; XI.
  This series contains records that do not pertain to any other series in the collection. They detail important aspects of the Alumni Association, but they do not fit with any defined series and are therefore kept together and arranged chronologically.
  - Loose Letters (Box 43, Folder 54)
  - University Honors College Scholars, 1983-1998 (Box 43, Folder 55)
  - Advisory Council on Regional Development Report, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 56)
  - Alcohol Policy, 1989-1992 (Box 43, Folder 57)
  - Indemnification Policy, 1990-1992 (Box 43, Folder 58)
  - Licensing, 1990-1996 (Box 43, Folder 59)
  - Gift Policies, 1992-1999 (Box 43, Folder 60)
  - Copyrights, 1994-1997 (Box 43, Folder 61)
  - General Development, 1995-1998 (Box 43, Folder 62)
  - Alumni Association Benchmarking, 1995-2005 (Box 43, Folder 63)
  - Newspaper Advertisement, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 64)
  - Planned Giving Policy, 1996-1999 (Box 43, Folder 65)
  - Chancellor Updates, 1998-1999 (Box 43, Folder 66)
  - National Survey of Fund Raising Executives, 1999-2000 (Box 43, Folder 67)
  - Pennsylvania Lobbying Regulations, 1999-2005 (Box 43, Folder 68-70)
  - Communications Grant, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 71)
  - September 11, 2001-2002 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Chancellor & Provost Calendar Request Forms, 2001-2005 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Catering Budget & Information, 2001-2010 (Box 44, Folder 3-4)
  - Alumni Attitude Survey, 2002-2003 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Tickets Returned & Not Used, 2004 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Tickets Returned & Not Used, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Corporate Sponsorship Research, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Facility Requests, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Association/Temple University Strategic Planning Meetings, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Data Analysis Reports, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 12-13)
  - Alumni Association Histories, 2007 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Association Page Markers (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Audio-Visual Materials, 1988-2011; XII.
  This series contains audio-visual material related to the Alumni Association. It is primarily VHS tapes but it also contains slides, CD-ROMS, DVDs, and digital camera memory cards.
  - Slides, 1.
    - Slide Show, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Andy's Speech to Trustees, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - CD-ROMs, 2.
    - Alumni Directory, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Alumni Association Presentation Files and Documents, 2002-2006, 2007-2008 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Alumni Today, 2009 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - SDHC Cards, 3.
    - Alumni Association Pictures, September 23, 2010 & January 4, 2011 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - DVD Videos, 4.
    - University of Pittsburgh History Videos, June 14, 2007 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - "John Ratzenberger's Made In America"- Cathedral of Learning, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - "Pitt's History Through Its People"
    - Alumni Association Membership Meeting & Membership Party, September 3, 2005
    - The Chancellor's Message to Alumni, 2006
    - The Chancellor's Message to Alumni, 2007
    - Lee Patouillet Farewell Reception and Dinner, August 1, 2008
  - VHS Cassettes, 5.
    - "The Spirit of Pittsburgh", 1989
    - "For You the Very Stars Are New"
    - "Follow Us Back to Pitt", August 26, 1988
    - "True Grit: The Dramatic Story of the 1989 Pittsburgh Panthers' Football Season", 1990
    - Homecoming, 1992
    - Alumni Association Slide Show, Fall 1992
    - Leaders Conference Slide Show, 1998
    - Alumni Association Photo Montage, May 1999
    - Alumni Association Slide Show, 1999
    - "A Salute to Our Volunteers", 1999-2000
    - Volunteer Training, June 21, 2000
    - "Celebration of Service", March 2001
    - "The University of Pittsburgh- A New Way of Thinking", August 16, 2001
    - "The University of Pittsburgh- A New Way of Thinking", October 2001
    - Insight Bowl- Phoenix, Arizona, December 26, 2002
    - Year in Review & Banner Opening, 2002
    - "Senate Journal" with Senator Jay Costa, Jr.- University of Pittsburgh, January 30, 2003
    - CBS "Morning Show"- Chancellor Nordenberg and Blue & Gold Society, December 10, 2003
    - Alumni Review, 2003
    - "A Salute to Our Volunteers", 2004
    - Alumni Leaders Luncheon- Eva T. Blum Special Tribute, April 24, 2004
    - Volunteer Year in Review, 2005
    - Discovery Weekend Highlight Video
    - Cecile Springer Interview
    - J. Roger Glunt Interview
    - Dr. Macy Levine Interview
    - Keith Schaefer Interview
    - Robert Lovett Interview
    - Cindy Roth Interview
    - Sam Zacharias Interview
    - Eva Blum Interview
    - Nancy Welfer Interview
    - Jim McCarl Interview
    - Generalovich Interview
    - Mr. and Mrs. William Trice Interview
    - Verklin Interview